travelchinaguide.com 2001-02-03

# Travel China Guide: Privacy

**Information Collected by TravelChinaGuide.com** Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to TravelChinaGuide.com. We have established the following statements in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and to ensure the integrity of the Internet. This TravelChinaGuide.com Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") explains the types of information we gather, what we do with it.

TravelChinaGuide.com collects two types of information about users: personal information (such as name and e-mail address) and aggregate information (such as information about how many users visit our sites on a daily basis). 

**Personal Information**

Personal information is collected when users voluntarily fill form. Personal information includes e-mail addresses, gender, birth date, interests, hobbies, travel preferences and any other user data. We may also receive personal usage and demographic information from our third-party partners, and we also collect e-mail addresses from users who send us support mail or request technical or other help. This information enables TravelChinaGuide.com to improve its sites to make your online visits more productive and enjoyable.

Our site's reservation form requires users to give us a valid e-mail address. We use customer e-mail addresses from the reservation form to inform you of travel information, problem solving, kind notice etc.

**Aggregate Information**

One method of collecting aggregate information about your activities online (such as the pages you access most frequently or the search terms you enter), and information volunteered by you (such as travelogue or feedback information). An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. The computers that deliver the Web pages to you automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from one of our sites, our servers log your IP address. TravelChinaGuide.com sites record IP addresses for the purpose of system administration and to provide aggregate data to advertisers about the volume of use on our sites. We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. In addition, your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

If you have any additional questions, please contact us: [webmaster@travelchinaguide.com](mailto:webmaster@travelchinaguide.com)
